Now we gotta do it
together.
Let's go.
Move it, Tom.
Come on, y'all.
Go.
Move it.
Your time is up.
You're on my time now.
This is what it means to get up and do
what you're supposed to do right away, not
monkeying around going back to the street
ways.
You've got to have the way you've been
brought up by your parents the right way.
The run is done 9, 10, 8 This is the
morning physical training, we call it PT
for short.
What this does, it sets the tone for the
day, wakes the mind.
It gets the body going, gets your fluids
going, gets your mind and your body in
gear, stimulates you, gets you
alive.
Ain't gonna be another easy day Ain't
gonna be another easy day
Settle to the right and platoon formation
with Deadly Shock Motivation I had
negative attitude as far as
I didn't really want the program because I
was scared of, you know, the type of
environment that I was in because I was
used to doing things the
way that I wanted to do it.
It's either I'm going to do what they tell
me to do or I'm not going to be able to go
home.
Superman Nothing to it.
Nothing to it.
Blue tights.
I'm a man.
Bullshit.
Ah ha.
Here we go.
This is not about dehumanizing.
This is not about degrading.
This is about teaching the mates to pay
attention, to listen, to think, to take
charge, take responsibility for their
life.